Guide to the Sports Memorabilia Collection SC0814
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Sports Memorabilia, Accession ARCH-2008-104
  - Official Souvenir Program
    - Washington Redskins vs. Buck Shaw's All Stars, First Annual Football Classic, August 28 [1940] (Box 11)
  - USFL KICKOFF Magazine
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Denver Gold, February 24, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Baltimore Stars, March 3, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Houston Gamblers, March 10, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Jacksonville Bulls, March 17, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. San Antonio Gunslingers, April 22, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Arizona Outlaws, April 27, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Los Angeles Express, May 11, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. Portland Breakers, June 2, 1985 (Box 11)
    - Oakland Invaders vs. New Jersey Generals, June 15, 1985 (2 copies) (Box 11)
  - Game Time: The official magazine of the World League
    - Sacramento Surge vs. Raleigh-Durham Skyhawks, March 23, 1991 (3 copies) (Box 11)
    - Sacramento Surge vs. Frankfurt Galaxy, April 13, 1991 (3 copies) (Box 11)
    - Sacramento Surge vs. Barcelona Dragons, April 27, 1991 (3 copies) (Box 11)
    - Sacramento Surge vs. Montreal Machine, May 4, 1991 (3 copies) (Box 11)
    - Sacramento Surge vs. London Monarchs, May 18, 1991 (3 copies) (Box 11)
    - Sacramento Surge vs. Birmingham Fire, March 21, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Sacramento Surge vs. Montreal Machine, April 4, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Sacramento Surge vs. Frankfurt Galaxy, May 9, 1992 (Box 11)
    - Sacramento Surge vs. Ohio Glory May, 16, 1992 (Box 11)
  - Arenaball: The official magazine of arena football
    - Chicago Bruisers vs. Denver Dynamite, June 20, 1987 (2 copies) (Box 11)
    - Pittsburgh Gladiators vs. Chicago Bruisers, June 26, 1987 (Box 11)
  - GameDay
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Washington Redskins, September 10, 1984 (Box 11)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. New Orleans Saints, September 16, 1984 (Box 11)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Tampa Bay Buccaneers, November 18, 1984 (Box 11)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Los Angeles Rams, December 14, 1984 (Box 11)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Atlanta Falcons, September 15, 1985 (Box 11)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Kansas City Chiefs, November 17, 1985 (Box 11)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Seattle Seahawks, November 25, 1985 (Box 11)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Los Angeles Rams, December 9, 1985 (Box 11)
    - San Francisco 49ers vs. Dallas Cowboys, December 22, 1985 (Box 11)
  - Miscellaneous College Basketball Guides
    - San Francisco State College, 1963-1964 (Box 13)
    - Stanford University Basketball, 1965-1966 (Box 13)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 1965-1966 (Box 13)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 1966-1967 (Box 13)
    - Stanford University, 1966-1967 (Box 13)
    - University of Southern California, 1967-1968 (Box 13)
    - University of Southern California, 1969-1970 (2 copies) (Box 13)
    - University of Southern California, 1970-1971 ( 2 copies) (Box 13)
    - Menlo College, 1982-1983 (Box 13)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 1984-1985 (Box 13)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 1985-1986 (Box 13)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 1990-1991 (Box 13)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 1991-1992 (Box 13)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 1992-1993 (Box 13)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 1993-1994 (Box 13)
    - Stanford University, 1994-1995 (Box 13)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 1994-1995 (Box 13)
    - Stanford University, 1995-1996 (Box 13)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 1995-1996 (Box 13)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, 1997-1998 (Box 13)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, 1998-1999 (Box 13)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 2002-2003 (Box 13)
    - Oregon State University, 2003-2004 (Box 13)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 2004-2005 (Box 13)
    - Oregon State University, 2005-2006 (Box 13)
    - University of California, Berkeley, 2006-2007 (Box 13)
- Sports Memorabilia, Accession ARCH-2016-021
  - College Basketball
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1924-26, 1924-1926 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1971-72, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1972-73, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1973-74, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1974-75, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1975-76, 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1976-77, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1977-78, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1978-79, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1979-80, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1981-82, 1981-1982 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1982-83, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1983-84, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1984-85, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1985-86, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1986-87, 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1987-88, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1988-89, 1988-1989 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1989-90, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1990-91, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1991-92, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1992-93, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1993-94, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1994-95, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1995-96, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1996-97, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1997-98, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1998-99, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 1999-00, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 2001-02, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 2002-03, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 2003-04, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 2004-05, 2004-2005 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 2005-06, 2005-2006 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 2006-07, 2006-2007 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 2007-08, 2007-2008 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 2011-12, 2011-2012 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 2012-13, 2012-2013 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 2013-14, 2013-2014 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Stanford University Men's Basketball Tickets, 2014-15, 2014-2015 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Stanford University Women's Basketball Tickets, 1978-79, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Stanford University Women's Basketball Tickets, 1979-80, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Stanford University Women's Basketball Tickets, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Cal Basketball Tickets, 2010-11, 2010-2011 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Cal Basketball Tickets, 2011-12, 2011-2012 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Cal Basketball Tickets, 2012-13, 2012-2013 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Cal Basketball Tickets, 2013-14, 2013-2014 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Cal Basketball Tickets, 2014-15, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - College Football
    - 2014 Mountain West Media Guide (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - 2014 Mountain West Media Guide (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Sports News 2014 College Football Preview (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Lindy's Pac-12 Football 2011 Vol. 25 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Athlon Sports Pac-12 Football 2014 Vol. 37 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Athlon Sports National College Football 2012 Vol.18 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - 2011 East-West Shrine Game Calendar (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - 2011 East-West Shrine Game Calendar (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - California Golden Bears Cal vs Utah, 2009-12-23 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - 2012 Official Notre Dame Football Yearbook (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Notre Dame Football 2013 Media Guide (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Athlon Sports National College Football 2013 Vol. 19 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Alabama vs. Texas A, 2014-10-18 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Alabama vs. Texas A, 2014-10-18 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Tennessee Insider 2010 Football Yearbook (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - 2007 Cal Golden Bears vs Louisiana Tech, 2007-09-15 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 2007 Cal Golden Bears vs. Arizona, 2007-09-22 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - 2007 Cal Golden Bears vs. Oregon State, 2007-10-13 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - 2007 Cal Golden Bears vs. Washington State, 2007-11-03 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - 2007 Cal Golden Bears vs. USC, 2007-11-10 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Syracuse University Football vs Washington, 2007-08-31 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Oregon Football vs. Cal, 2007-09-29 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - 2007 Arizona vs. Cal, 2007-10-27 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - 2007 Arizona vs. Washington, 2007-10-13 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - 2007 Arizona vs. Trojans, 2007-11-22 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - USC Trojans vs Arizona Wildcats, 2007-10-13 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - UCLA Bruins vs Washington Huskies, 2007-09-22 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - UCLA Bruins vs Arizona State Sun Devils, 2007-11-10 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - UCLA Bruins vs Oregon Ducks, 2007-11-24 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Utah Red Zone vs. UCLA, 2007-09-15 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Arizona vs UCLA, 2007-11-03 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Penn State vs. Oregon State Kickoff Magazine, 2008-09-06 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Baylor vs Washington, 2008-09-13 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - TCU vs. Stanford, 2008-09-13 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Purdue vs. Oregon, 2008-09-13 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Maryland vs Cal, 2008-09-13 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - BYU vs. UCLA, 2008-09-13 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - 2008 Lobo Football The Arizona Game, 2008-09-13 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - UCLA Bruins vs. Arizona Wildcats, 2008-09-20 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - UCLA Bruins vs. Fresno State Bulldogs, 2008-09-27 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Cal Golden Bears vs Colorado State, 2008-09-27 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Utah vs Oregon State, 2008-10-02 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Arizona Sun Devils vs Arizona, 2007-12-01 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Wisconsin vs Washington State, 2007-09-01 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Cougar Illustrated BYU vs Arizona, 2007-09-01 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Cal vs Tennessee, 2007-09-01 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Cincinnati vs. Oregon State, 2007-09-06 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - CSU vs. Cal, 2007-09-08 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - UCLA Bruins vs BYU Cougars, 2007-09-08 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Cal vs. Arizona State, 2008-10-04 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - UCLA vs Washington State, 2008-10-04 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - UCLA vs Stanford, 2008-10-18 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Cal vs UCLA, 2008-10-25 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Cal vs Oregon, 2008-11-01 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - UCLA vs Oregon State, 2008-11-08 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Cal vs Washington, 2008-12-06 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - UCLA vs Tennessee Volunteers, 2008-09-01 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Cal vs Michigan, 2008-08-30 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Cavaliers vs. Southern California Trojans, 2008-08-30 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Oregon vs Arizona, 2008-11-15 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Oregon State vs Cal, 2009-11-07 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Oregon vs Arizona State, 2009-11-14 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Arizona vs Cal, 2009-11-14 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - UCLA Bruins vs Arizona State Sun Devils, 2009-11-21 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Washington vs Washington State, 2009-11-28 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Washington vs Cal, 2009-12-05 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - USC Trojans vs Arizona Wildcats, 2009-12-05 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Bronco Breakdown Oregon State, 2010-09-25 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - USC vs Cal, 2009-10-03 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Oregon vs Washington State, 2009-10-03 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - UCLA vs Oregon, 2009-10-10 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - UCLA vs Cal, 2009-10-17 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Washington State vs Cal, 2009-10-24 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - USC vs Oregon, 2009-10-24 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - UCLA vs Washington Huskies, 2009-11-07 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - SMU vs Washington State, 2010-09-18 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - USC Trojans vs San Jose State Spartans, 2009-09-05 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Eastern Washington vs Cal, 2009-09-12 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Eastern Washington vs Cal, 2009-09-12 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Arizona State vs ULM, 2009-09-19 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - UCLA vs Kansas State, 2009-09-19 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - USC vs Washington State, 2009-09-26 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Oregon vs Cal, 2009-09-26 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - USC vs Cal, 2009-10-03 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - UCLA vs Washington State Hall of Fame weekend, 2010-10-02 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - USC vs. Washington Huskies, 2010-10-02 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - UCLA vs Cal, 2010-10-09 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Maryland vs. Cal, 2009-09-05 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Boise State Bronco Breakdown, 2009-09-03 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - UCLA Bruins vs. San Diego Aztecs, 2009-09-05 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - USC Bruins vs Houston Cougars, 2010-09-18 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - USC Trojans vs. Virginia Cavaliers, 2010-09-11 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Colorado vs. Cal, 2010-09-11 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - UC Davis vs. Cal, 2010-09-04 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Oklahoma State vs. Washington State, 2010-09-04 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - University of Toledo Rocket Football, 2010-09-03 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Washington vs. Cal, 2010-11-27 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Oregon vs Cal, 2010-11-13 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Arizona State vs Cal, 2010-10-23 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - USC Trojans vs Cal, 2010-10-16 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - USC Trojans vs ASU Sun Devils, 2010-11-06 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Cougar Football Washington State vs California, 2010-11-06 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Oregon vs New Mexico, 2010-09-04 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Nevada Football vs California, 2010-09-17 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - UNLV vs Oregon State, 2009-09-12 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Wisconsin vs. Oregon State, 2011-09-10 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - USC Trojans vs. Utah Utes, 2011-09-10 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Presbyterian vs. California, 2011-09-17 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - UCLA Bruins vs. Texas Longhorns, 2011-09-17 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Illinois vs. Arizona, 2011-09-17 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - USC Trojans vs. Syracuse Orange, 2011-09-17 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - BYU vs. Utah, 2011-09-17 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Nebraska vs Washington, 2011-09-17 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Oregon State vs UCLA, 2011-09-24 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - USC Trojans vs. Oregon Ducks, 2010-10-30 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - UCLA Bruins vs. Oregon State Beavers, 2010-11-06 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Oklahoma State Cowboys vs. Arizona Wildcats, 2011-09-08 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Colorado vs. California, 2011-09-10 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Stanford vs. Duke, 2011-09-11 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - UCLA Bruins vs. San Jose State Spartans, 2011-09-10 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - USC Trojans vs. Minnesota, 2011-09-03 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Houston vs. UCLA, 2011-09-03 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Fresno vs. California, 2011-09-03 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Oregon State vs. BYU, 2011-10-15 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - USC vs. California, 2011-10-13 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - UCLA vs. Washington State, 2011-10-08 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Oregon State vs. Arizona, 2011-10-08 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - USC vs Arizona, 2011-10-01 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - FIU vs. Marshall, 2011-12-20 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - UCLA vs. Colorado, 2011-11-19 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - USC vs. Washington, 2011-11-12 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Oregon State vs. California, 2011-11-12 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - UCLA vs. California, 2011-10-29 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - UCLA vs. Utah, 2012-10-13 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - BYU vs. Oregon State, 2012-10-13 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - USC vs. Colorado, 2012-10-20 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Washington vs. Oregon State, 2012-10-27 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Washington vs. California, 2012-11-02 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - USC vs. Oregon, 2012-11-03 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - UCLA vs. Arizona, 2012-11-03 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Oregon vs. California, 2012-11-10 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - USC vs. Arizona State, 2012-11-10 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Washington vs.Utah, 2012-11-10 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Washington vs. Colorado, 2011-10-15 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Pitt vs. Utah, 2011-10-15 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Utah vs. California, 2011-10-22 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Oregon State vs. Nicholls State, 2012-09-01 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - USC vs. Hawaii, 2012-09-01 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Utah State vs Utah, 2012-09-07 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Oregon State vs. Wisconsin, 2012-09-08 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Southern Utah vs. California, 2012-09-08 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - UCLA vs. California, 2012-10-06 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Oregon State vs. Washington State, 2011-10-06 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Washington vs. USC, 2012-10-13 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - USC vs. California, 2012-09-22 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - UCLA vs. Oregon, 2012-09-22 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Arizona State vs. California, 2012-09-29 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Mizzou vs. Arizona State, 2012-09-15 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - UCLA vs. Houston, 2012-09-15 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Fresno State vs. Colorado, 2012-09-15 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - BYU vs. Washington State, 2012-08-30 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Arizona State vs. Illinois, 2012-09-08 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Arizona State vs. Northern Arizona, 2012-08-30 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Arizona vs Oregon State, 2012-09-29 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Arizona vs. Oklahoma State, 2012-09-08 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - UNLV vs. Washington State, 2012-09-14 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Arizona vs. Washington, 2012-10-20 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Arizona vs. Arizona State, 2012-11-23 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Arizona vs. Toledo, 2012-09-01 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Arizona vs. South Carolina State, 2012-09-15 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - UCLA vs Nevada, 2013-08-31 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Northwestern vs. California, 2013-08-31 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Mile High Sports Magazine - College Football Preview, 2013-08-01 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Portland State vs. California, 2013-09-07 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - USC vs. Washington State, 2013-09-07 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Ohio State vs. California, 2013-09-14 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - USC vs. Boston College, 2013-09-14 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Washington State vs. Cal, 2013-10-05 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - USC vs. Arizona, 2013-10-10 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - UCLA vs. California, 2013-10-12 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Oregon State vs. California, 2013-10-19 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Arizona vs. California, 2013-11-02 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Washington State vs. Arizona State, 2013-10-31 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - USC vs. Utah, 2013-10-26 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - 2013 USC Media Guide (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Washington State vs. California, 2013-10-05 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - UCLA vs. New Mexico, 2013-09-21 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - San Diego State Football Yearbook 2013 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - BYU vs. Utah, 2013-09-21 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - USC vs. Utah State, 2013-09-21 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - UCLA vs. Washington Huskies, 2013-11-15 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - USC vs. California, 2013-11-09 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - UCLA Bruins vs. Colorado Buffaloes, 2013-11-02 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Arizona vs. UTSA, 2013-09-14 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Arizona vs. Washington State, 2013-11-16 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - USC Trojans vs. Fresno State, 2014-08-30 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Northwestern vs. California, 2014-08-30 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - UTSA vs. Arizona, 2014-09-04 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - New Mexico vs. Arizona, 2014-09-06 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Sacramento vs. California, 2014-09-06 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - UCLA Bruins vs. Memphis Tigers, 2014-09-06 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Washington vs. California, 2014-10-11 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - UCLA vs. Oregon, 2014-10-11 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Washington State vs. California, 2014-10-04 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - UCLA vs. Utah, 2014-10-04 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - USC vs. Arizona State, 2014-10-04 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - USC vs. Oregon State, 2014-09-27 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Colorado vs. California, 2014-09-27 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Arizona Sun Devils vs. UCLA, 2014-09-27 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Washington State vs. Oregon, 2014-09-20 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Washington State vs. Portland, 2014-09-13 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Arizona vs. Oregon, 2014-09-13 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - 2014 Colorado Football Game Program (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - UCLA vs. Arizona State, 2014-11-23 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Mile High Sports Magazine - College and High School Football Preview, 2014-08-01 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Washington State vs. Rutgers, 2014-08-28 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - USC Trojans vs. Colorado, 2014-10-18 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - UCLA vs. California, 2014-10-18 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Washington State vs. California, 2014-10-25 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - UCLA vs. Arizona, 2014-11-01 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Washington State vs. USC, 2014-11-01 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Oregon State vs. California, 2014-11-01 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - USC Trojans vs. California, 2014-11-13 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - BYU vs. California, 2014-11-29 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Arizona vs. UNLV, 2014-08-29 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Arizona vs. Colorado, 2014-11-08 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - MLB
    - All-Star Game, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Cal State League, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Dodgers, 1930-1969 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Giants, 1958-1969 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Red Sox, 1940-1957 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - World Series, 1990-2012 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Scorecards - Giants, 1957-1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Scorecards - Misc, 1970-1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - MLB - All-star game, 1961-1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - MLB-A's, 1972-2007 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - MLB-Dodgers, 1956-08, 1956-2008 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - MLB-Giants, 1958-12, 1958-2012 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - MLB-Padres, 1991-06, 1991-2006 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - MLB-Red Soy, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - MLB-Yankees, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - MLB-Misc, 1970-07, 1970-2007 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Yearbooks-Dodgers, 1959-66, 1959-1966 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Yearbooks-Giants, 1957-70, 1957-1970 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Yearbooks-Misc, 1961-76, 1961- 1976 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - NBA
  - NFL
    - Super Bowl Ephemera
      - Seat Cushion - Super Bowl, 1988 (Box 1)
      - Seat Cushion - Super Bowl, 1987 (Box 1)
      - Seat Cushion - Super Bowl, 1988 (Box 4)
      - Seat Cushion - Super Bowl, 1993 (Box 2)
      - Seat Cushion - Super Bowl, 1996 (Box 2)
      - Seat Cushion - Super Bowl, 1997 (Box 3)
    - San Francisco 49ers 2011 Media Guide (Box 11, Folder 1)